let quiz = [
    {
        question: "What country was Adolf Hitler the chancellor of?",
        option: [
            "Russia",
            "Germany",
            "France",
            "Belgum",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What was Benito Mussolini’s nationality?",
        option: [
            "Italian",
            "Turkish",
            "American",
            "Austria",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Between 1945 and 1946, in which country did the famous Nuremberg Trial take place?",
        option: [
            "Russia",
            "Germany",
            "Poland",
            "Austria",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What was Charles de Gaulle’s nationality?",
        option: [
            "Belgum",
            "German",
            "Greek",
            "French",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "The Cold War saw the United States and... face?",
        option: [
            "Russia",
            "France",
            "China",
            "North Korea",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What year did the USSR break up?",
        option: ["1989", "2000", "1991", "USSR still exist"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What does the term USSR mean?",
        option: [
            "Russia",
            "Union of the Slovenian and Swedish Kingdoms",
            "Union of Soviet Socialist Republics",
            "Unification of the Serbian and Slovak Republic",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What year was the Berlin Wall destroyed?",
        option: ["Wall still exist", ".1989", "2001", "1945"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "In what year did the war in Algeria end?",
        option: ["1989", "1973", "she was never at war", "1962"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How many seven-year-olds has François Mitterrand done?",
        option: ["Three", "Two", "one", "none"],
        answer: 2,
    },
];